let's get ready for the show let's
welcome our guest you want to say his
name Mr Adrian truth okay welcome give
it up for Adrian truth what's going on
what's going on
everybody sorry about that it was it you
know the the AI technology it doesn't
pronounce all the names right but you
know we were just trying something
different you know but uh that that made
me laugh a little
bit yeah
I was cringing when they when she said
the voices I was
like
yeah sorry about
that but it's all good but you're here
and uh thank you so much for for uh
coming to hustle Zone TV oh no no
problem thank you so the first question
that we would like to ask you um that we
ask all of our guests on hustle own TV
um you know mainly because we we are a
living documentary is what is your story
so start from way back and bring us up
to terms to how you became who you are
today okay uh well if you want to go way
way back I would say it started out um
when I was in my grandfather's choir um
he was the pastor of my church and you
couldn't really just do anything you
couldn't just sit back and just praise
God you have to uh do something so uh he
made my family either you had to be a
Usher
or you know do something so uh we
started a choir and threw me in there
and at the time I was probably
like 10 for real it's quiet didn't
really talk a lot and that kind of gave
me my
voice yeah so I started there and uh it
gave me the confidence to to start doing
it for real for real and started going
to high school and formed a group in
high school and people started receiving
uh the vocals in a in a positive light
and after that I
just started taking off a little bit
taking it more seriously started putting
out content and yeah and
I guess I would say here here I am now
just started linking up with people
around the city and befriending fellow
artists and getting on their music
and yeah now wow that's I here and now
you're
here and how did you know Adrian how did
you know um that that's what you wanted
to do like of course you're in the
church you're singing Because at that
point of course you're you're young
right and you're doing what your parents
want to do like all of us
do but like how did you know what I mean
and uh how did you know that that was
what you like what made you feel that
that was for you that that really
touched your heart and you're like this
is what I need to
do well it was more so I don't know if
it was a mixture between Me growing up
in church and you know that that whole
spiritual
upliftment that that it gives you and
yeah and when I'm singing what it does
to people and you get that reaction that
energy it resonates through people so
when I received that energy it just like
made me feel feel good and and to know
like that what I'm doing is something
that I love doing and it makes other
people feel good just as much as it
makes me feel good so that
definitely helped spark that that light
bulb to definitely do it now do you
think that um do you think that your
life was destined um for this journey I
mean like we all have a calling but um I
I think and believe that um some of us
are made for some of us think we have a
calling for specific things um and
others are just made for it do you did
do you believe that you were made for
for this life I believe that I was for
sure created to to entertain or just
bring my perspective of what I do into
the Universe I just want to just put out
positive energy and I just want to be
myself and in the
meantime uh Inspire others to to do
whatever they want to do because I might
you know Inspire somebody
through my music
to to do whatever they want to do and it
might not even be music it might be uh
painting it might be uh become a doctor
like weird stuff happens when you
inspire people uh movies inspire me
other artists don't even inspire me
sometimes it can be uh someone I just
met the other day and we have a
conversation and the conversation that
we had might have sparked something a
idea to write a song or to paint
something so yeah it's
yeah so Adrian when you when you came to
that point of your calling what was your
goal what was your next goal what was it
that you said Okay I want to sing this
is what makes me happy I'm creating
change I'm creating love I'm creating
peace with my music what was your goal
for you my goal was to record a song at
that at that point in time my goal was
just to record something and have people
hear it and see what they what they
think it didn't go too too far ahead in
that because at the time I was in my
early teens so I just wanted for the
most part
validation and uh the the more I I did
it the more I I seen that I didn't
really get too many negative uh feedback
so I'm like okay that's cool and
then that's that's the green light yeah
I got the green light got got the green
light a few times so uh after that I I
wanted to to actually leave Impressions
on people when I actually like did music
so it's it's one thing to to create
something and people like it sounds good
but it's another thing when it's
like a soundtrack to the
to whatever they're going through in
that in that time period whether it be
love making or you know something like
really serious political or
yeah now what oh go ahead Monica no go
ahead I'm good okay sorry uh what is
your artistic process you know um
whether you know because I know that you
do graphic design and whatnot but how do
you normally come up with your ideas and
how how does that all come into
fruition um um I'm a real big um like
concept person so like it it varies like
if it's if it's artwork then I will come
at the idea of of it like if I draw
let's say like a a a flower right
instead of making it look like a typical
just like a
flower and nice little pretty colors I
would probably make the flow like melt
or something make it look like it's
dripping melting just to give it like a
different spin on it or make it look
like it's wilting away and then turning
into something totally different like
maybe turning into Like a Phoenix or
something or uh and then I translate
that too in my music so uh when I
usually do music I try
to do it in a perspective to where it's
it's
not the tip like it can mean more than
one thing it can be like uh let me use
an example like okay just like how
Prince does like Little Red Corvette
like
he talks about a woman but it's she's
talking about a car and comparing her to
like this fast thing so yeah that's what
I like to do I like to
to mix it up a little bit like that yeah
for sure that's nice and Adrian in your
music after you got to the point that
you're recording and you started running
into people and people that obviously
are inspiring and whether they're up
here or down here it doesn't matter but
who was it that really like you know
when you get into that moment and then
you're like wow like I'm there you know
what I mean who was it that when they
saw your music and you for you you
personally that made you feel like wow
like these people really love what I'm
doing and and so who was that person
that gave you that kind of stroke but at
the same time what was the encouragement
and advice that you got from them that
made you even more stronger as an
artist well it's a few but I would say
for sure for sure when I uh got the
validation from Tech 9 and he's like
yeah a big big bro to me Hometown hero
he's from the same city as me and uh
he's like the number one independent rap
artist in the world and that's that's a
huge accomplishment uh got his own label
Strange Music and when he heard my music
and he was like man I want to get you on
my stuff man I think you're like
incredible and then to actually get on a
song with him and then uh be able to do
a song with him and Bo to men which is
like crazy as heck and to meet W and uh
sit down with him and chop it up and him
telling me like you got an incredible
voice and yeah like you were one of the
main reasons why we got on the song so
that was like a a big uh ego boost and a
a verification that I'm I'm on the right
path so yeah now the music industry is
um I mean a lot of things have changed a
lot of artists are you know going
independent uh and you know for the most
part when there're more when they're
being when artists are being signed to
record labels you know they have these
360 deals and some of these deals are
not the greatest right um and a lot of
artists you know get into the business
they get these huge advances and then
they never recoup on on their royalties
Etc um you know how are you making it
through this industry because it's so
you know in a lot of ways it's brutal
but if you can make it
past um you know what if you can become
really successful um and make it past it
it could be very you know luxurious for
for a lot or promising for a lot of
artists but how are you making it
through uh some of those con
streets I'm actually just a student I'm
continuing to be a student so I'm
learning as I go and I know people that
are assigned and I'm taking advice from
them and seeing what they're doing
seeing what works and see what doesn't
work so it's not working for them I'mma
try this other path and see where it
takes me so it's all my career is all
built off of
relationships and uh me being humble and
hungry
and trying to you know get to that next
that next uh destination so yeah it's
not it's not a Sprint it's Marathon so I
know I'm I'm in it for the long haul so
for sure for
sure I just wanted to shout out Ivonne
in the comments much love and thank you
for being here and everybody that's
watching us with a and truth and Ron pza
myself on
exclus yes so I think it's your question
or my question
go ahead Ryan okay so okay so you you
said you know you're you're you're a
student and um now I'm not trying to be
negative or you know say that you know
your career is not going to uh be like
let's say a Michael Jackson's or
whatever nobody's gonna be Michael
Jackson there's only one Michel Jackson
he's so good answer we'll take it so I I
mean in that you know when you you get
into the music industry and you're still
learning um what do you think what are
some tips that you could even for
someone that's entering in the industry
with the stuff that you have learned um
you know how can you what can you tell
uh some of the younger uh musicians
coming up you know what they'll have to
do to maintain a career um in the music
industry you have to be a good human
being uh to build great relationships
long lasting relationships and you're
going to have to have a a good solid
team around you and you're GNA have to
have a nice little budget because you
can be talented and if you ain't got the
bag then you're gonna be kind of like
you
know trying to win a lottery so uh yeah
those are just a little few things that
I think that I know that you're G to
need to have to have definitely to have
some stay in power for sure talent
definitely helps but if you got talent
and Capital then you're going up right
right exactly
exactly Adrian when it comes to your
family what type of support do they give
you and what is it that you want them to
learn from you and
your not struggles but growing as a
person and to be doing something that
you love and are passionate about right
uh my family is definitely supportive uh
they they kind of just let me do me
because they know that I'm kind of
stubborn and I kind of just like if I
have a vision I'm just gonna go for it
and they know that I'm not gonna do
anything negative so they're just gonna
let me do me and they just they're gonna
back me 100% so yeah and uh I'm sure
that by me doing what I'm doing is
inspiring them to do whatever they are
trying to do in life and definitely
never too late for them to do whatever
they want to do my mom uh just uh
graduated college like two years
ago never never never too late never
it's so true so true so how are you um
or I guess let me rephrase this
question you know besides the artist who
is Adrian
truth Adrian truth is a a
father um I have a a a son he is about
to be eight months and a week so that's
definitely something that I am and it's
a new incredible experience uh Adrian
truth is a humble human being someone
that you can just talk to
um
and it's kind of weird talking about
myself I have to like have you ask
somebody that I know uh who who am I but
I know I feel like I'm I'm a decent
human
being
yeah great answer great answer um Adan
if you could collaborate with
somebody who who would be that dream
person and I that's a hard question
because I'm pretty sure there's a lot of
people that most likely give you
inspiration but someone that you know
that you just it's on your bucket list
like you just have to have it done I
mean if you were to do a a a dead dead
or alive because I I want to work with
way more people that are not living than
are living oh okay I got you that's I
would want to work with like a mar gay I
work you know a Leah uh
a lot of people but I'm I'm a fan of a
lot of new newer artists I'm a fan of
like Jana Aika I'm a fan of uh the new
wave of R&B that's that's out right now
for
sure yeah Anderson pack is incredible uh
I can go on and on and on but
yeah so I like and speaking of which
because I think that a lot of the music
nowadays
um most of it you know it's easy to get
on to Fruity Loops or whatever uh
sequencer and put some beats together
sing on top of it put it out and put it
on Tik Tock and then it goes viral and
then you're famous um you know it it
seems like the the things have changed
but the times of
mtown um where you know mtown you would
have to wait you know a few years before
you even dropped a record they were
developing you teaching you how to speak
and all of that stuff do you think that
that will ever come back in music where
you know with the with the pace at which
the the internet and everything is going
do you think that there's still room for
artistic
development I would never uh vote out
artistic uh development I think it's
definitely
necessary um yeah definitely but as far
as how
slow the process was putting the music
together like you said like couple years
and then they'll put out a project or a
single um I think that's gone with the
Doos that's I don't think that's gonna
happen any anytime soon the internet is
never slowing down so uh as long as the
internet exists
then content is going to keep strolling
out yeah Adrian is there a song that you
would say best
describes
you wow let's say in the music that
you've made right okay let's narrow it
down let just narrow it
that um I don't know I mean like all of
my songs are kind of like they vary
because I have a song called sway that's
pretty chill and I will probably say
sway probably because everybody says I'm
a chill person so yeah okay okay awesome
now you being you you mentioned that
you're a father I'm a father um your
your son is uh you said son right
hopefully I I said that right so sorry I
just had a made I'm like you say
daughter or son but your son um you know
what are some of the values
that you know based on your life
experience and you know how you've
gotten this far in your career um what
sort of advice would you give your son
when your son comes of age that he can
kind of comprehend you know his life
Journey right well I would definitely
tell him to never
settle uh don't compromise your um your
goals and your
dreams uh follow them and be authentic
to who you are for sure because there's
only one you so you might as well be
that
person great and yeah definitely
um if you had a
choice and you didn't do like the type
of music that you actually sing when it
comes to R&B or raer in general that
you're around
if you were to do something that's
opposite of what you
did what would that be and with
who that's a good
question still in the music genre right
you were talking about music yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I think I will probably do like
some electronic
music oh okay and I don't know with you
with who but would probably like collab
with like somebody uh like Tam and Paulo
or somebody that would be dope okay okay
and now I just want to kind of change
the tone of this interview for for a
minute and talk about um what because
all of our lives have
changed um we have covid that dropped
you know that really stumped the plans
for a lot of people and we
also uh um we also have been protesting
in especially in the black community
been protesting a lot of people are
protesting for God knows what but we
know that black lives matter has been a
topic um with countless videos of you
know whether it's carens exploding you
know on people or you know you know like
they don't want to wear masks and then
you have Karen's exploding on you know
people of color um and then you have um
you know police with George uh Floyd and
a few other videos that have been coming
out um you know with you you seeing
police brutality in real time you know
how does that impact you U being a
person of
color uh it has been impacting me uh
tremendously and it's been impacting me
before Co um you can't really Escape
being black uh
it's just more so the fact that it's um
finally it's like the boy uh who kind of
not even the boy Cry Wolf like we've
been crying this whole time that it's
been going on and now that Co is kind of
like a double-edged sword it's a
blessing in disguise because now
everybody the whole world can sit their
ass down and and see what's really going
on and they don't have a regular lives
to distract them from what's actually
going on so now they see that we're not
like crying wolf we're not telling lies
like this is really going on and it's
been going on before I was even existed
so yeah um yeah it definitely affects me
for
sure and just want sorry I I just wanted
to have a follow-up uh question um with
that being said you know what how have
you been
like with all the protesting and and
everyone kind of taking to social media
you know in what ways have you are you
participating in the protest and the
riots or or not the riots I don't know
definitely not participating in any
riots yeah but I was just I had to bring
that back there but yeah like are you
participating in the protesting or in
what ways are you you know uh using your
platform to bring light around some of
these issues right I'm definitely have
been putting stuff on my Ig my stories
I I do it in a in a way that's that's
subtle I will wear a hat that says like
1619 and if you get it you get it if you
don't you
don't yeah definitely so yeah that
that's how I do things I I do things in
a kind
of slick witty
way yeah I feel
you sad you ever find
yourself and and I asked this question
because I've see it with my friends and
Ryan of course and um do you ever find
that you're in a position sometimes
that as your care goes and with all
these protests that's have been
happening and people are trying to be
much more aware do you find that you're
ever in a position that you notice that
you're beginning to see the colors of
people that you've known for so long for
example friends or and you have to
explain to them does that
become does that become how would I word
it hard to have to constantly be
explaining it to people I mean there are
some that don't explain it because they
feel like you know what just figure it
out kind of thing which is totally
understandable but you know sometimes
for me that I have question questions
I'll ask Ryan and Ryan will definitely
you know explain it but do you ever have
those issues that you know you have
people that are close to you that just
don't get it and you're put in a
position kind
of how do you deal with that you know uh
no not really because a lot of the
people that I'm around either look like
me or grew up around people that look
like me so I got I feel like the people
that don't get it for the most
part didn't grow up around
minorities yeah so it's kind of it's
kind of hard it's a disconnect for for
people like that and you know maybe on
my Facebook page I have friends on there
that show their true colors but that's a
easy you know
unfollow but as far as like close
friends that I see or talk to on a
day-to-day basis no we don't we don't
have those conversations because we we
already know the answer you already know
right right right okay yeah that makes
sense so uh we've gotten to the first
part of our interview so we're going to
be uh heading into our hold on a second
let me pull this up our lightning round
wooo lightning
so um before we get into the lightning
round I just want to shout out everybody
in the comments uh this was a great
interview uh with Adrian Truth uh we
have uh Ivonne in the house and she's
saying uh she wanted to tell you that
hey Adrien you are
cute thank you she says good advice just
sent it to a young cousin of mine um
Pico freckles who is a
freestyle uh uh freestyle singer I call
it singing poetry beautiful she also
says uh that's cool me want to do that
uh let me and then she said please ask
Adrian if he knows his genetics his
genetic history I'm curious because he
um because he he can pass for different
ethnic groups do you want to answer that
question that's hilarious everybody
always ask me that
so uh the most part I mean my mom and
dad are black but I
know further down the line I got uh some
some slave masters in me and
uh and a few other stuff but yeah I'm
like for the most part like black yeah
straight up and same with me I got my my
ancestry DNA and yeah I was like oh snap
I got you know Irish Scottish I'm like
oh bunch of bunch of slave masters
nothing
much you
know but it is what it is yeah it is
what it is so okay um so first
question Michael Jackson or
Prince I'm G say prince so hard it is
hard it is hard but then like the more
and more I I get older and like
appreciate what they both
do Michael Jackson is just like a
another he's an alien and then I I
consider like I
consider Prince he's he's like a a
actual human being but he's like on
another level too yeah but he like can
play every instrument he's like a a
musician's musician like he can do
everything writes all of his music
performs it uh
assembles everything you know he
orchestrates all the stuff so yeah I
would say prince for
sure because Michael Jackson had songs
written for him all of his hits for the
most part somebody else wrote for him
all of Prince's hits he wrote himself
and he wrote other people's hits so got
you I got you talk talking or
texting if you ask me this on another
day
it just depends right now I say
texter it depends it depends it depends
how I
feel from a scale from uh from a scale
one to 10 are you uh where are you in
terms of
driving on a scale from one to 10 10
being like the greatest driver in the
world and one being like uh blind and
I'm just about to crash into a ditch I
would say like 15 I'm
incredible okay oh my back go ahead no
go ahead go ahead sorry um beanies or
baseball
hats beanies that's a hard one right I
know it just depends on the on the the
situation right people don't get that
and people laugh because I love to wear
beanies like obsessed I even knit my own
beanie
and I give them way love it do and I
love baseball hats too so it really
depends on you exactly thanks for saying
that um also if you could travel back in
time what period would you go
to okay this is hard because are we
talking about in America because I'm not
going to far back in
America I can't go
back then if it's if I gota go back in
time in America where I am right now I'm
going I'm going back to like three days
ago I can't I can't go back to yeah yeah
I got you I got you if if I looked a
different complexion then I can go back
as far as I want to go in America and
I'll be kind of kind of Gucci
yeah yeah well I'll leave it up to you
okay
um so oh then yeah well you know what
I'll just say because we could go back
like people don't know like black people
were here the original people on the
Earth so I mean we could go back to when
we because we were traveling to North
America you know way before Columbus so
I mean we could like we could travel
like maybe 5,000 100,000 trillion years
ago and but like yeah no black people
don't like I when every every time I
watch uh
Back to the Future I'm like yeah that's
not
me yeah we can get on some omx you know
the omx was over here before a lot of
people there yeah you look at all those
big old stone heads that were here way
before a lot of these people and they
were Black Faces big
noses all the features of a black person
so straight up straight
up and how about first celebrity
crush first celebrity
crush I'm G have to say Aaliyah that was
she
was yeah I love
her still I still do
she I painted
her did oh I see her in the background
in the back in little corner oh yeah
that's her I got you okay
Dawn or
dusk you said say that one more time
dusk I'm G say I say Don yeah Don for
sure yeah and um place that you uh place
you most want to travel
to I want to go see the pyramid so I'll
say Egypt for sure or Great Wall China
oh yeah man and um finally what is your
favorite
quote my favorite
quotes I got a I got a few but my right
now I would say uh be an asset not a
liability be an asset not a liability
liability I love yeah I like that one
and um you know and we always ask this
funny question but um is it okay for
vegans to eat animal
crackers no no that's kind of morbid
actually shaming us shaming us for
eating meat but y'all eating something
that's not meat but it looks like you
know what I'm saying that's kind of
weird I understand I got I Jud I
judge said said well that that wraps up
our our interview thank you so much for
for coming to hustle Zone
exclusiva um and uh did you like the
experience yes it was great thank you
for having me it was uh I had fun for
sure awesome and um you know what sort
of projects do you have um that you want
to promote right now I'm working on
my album It's Gonna uh well it hasn't
been announced yet but it will be coming
out fall time so I'm dropping singles
right now and it's going to
be I I'm pretty excited about this
project for sure every song is going to
have its own individual artwork so I'm
uh working on that now so whenever you
uh buy I'm gonna have each artwork is
gonna have its own prints and you can
buy the print and when you get the print
you get the uh song for free so oh W GNA
be 11 Tracks so 11 different paintings
and yeah it's going to be going to be
pretty dope it's going to be called uh
the art project and it's art art adri
ran truth so yeah awesome where can we
find you on social media for those who
who don't know everywhere is going to be
Adrian truth a d r i a an truth
Tru uh yeah and I will be posting daily
so uh hit me up and I will be there
awesome so Adria before you leave um
because you're a part of the industry
you know what a call and response is so
you know it's just tradition of uh
anyone that hops on any show on hustle
on TV that we do the call and response
so um uh we're gonna say welcome to the
and then you need to scream well we'll
all scream hustle Zone as loud as we can
so ready for that are you ready are you
ready cuz I don't know if these uh
monitors
can
so one two three welcome to the
hustle we we gon have to do that again
yeah yeah yeah
so that was I was I was making sure that
we was gonna do do it at the same time
oh okay okay yeah yeah so let's we we
were a sake so we'll try it one more
time so welcome to the
hustle thank you so much Adrian and like
like you said you guys can find him
anywhere Adrian truth um and then we
also have the links in the description
thank you so much Adrian for hopping in
no problem man awesome have a good one
yeah that was a great interview e it was
darling it was and Adrian is such a
sweet heart and such a motivation for
anybody that does what he does so I love
a good you know what I like about Adrian
um I like that
um he is he he says he's humble but he
is humble like through his demeanor but
when you listen to his music man if I
was Adrian if I had his looks and I if I
could sing like him I'd be like I'm not
humble I'm the best I'm the best that
ever was best that ever but no he's
really good he's humble you know he's
smart and and I think that I think just
listening to his music he's gonna be um
everyone should know his name and he's
just going to be a Powerhouse so you
guys need to definitely check him out um
like I said the links are in the
description and for those people that um
haven't done so already you guys can
also find the links to donate either via
PayPal to hustle Zone TV or you can go
to um our GoFundMe page let me just that
that link right there where is that go
me go
me so make sure you guys check that out
right now um and then um yeah but thank
you guys all for for joining in now
tomorrow we usually do this Fridays and
Saturdays um you know and um sometimes
it skips depending on on what people
book
but you guys definitely want to uh uh go
to if you if you need to be notified
just follow us follow us on hustles Zone
TV follow us on um on YouTube follow us
on Facebook follow us on Instagram and
Instagram and stuff like that and you'll
be able to get notified when we are
going to be dropping another interview
so tomorrow I'll let Monica tell people
a little bit about our guest for
tomorrow tomorrow we have a gentleman a
good friend of mine Jason lamcraft
um a very talented painter um come
tomorrow um because he has new work that
he would love to show us and you know my
goodness bottom line you just got to
show up
tomorrow because Jason um I've got to
known him over the years and and I
actually did a show with him
before and the difference from what he
was painting for before to now is just
unbelievable and you know people are
getting to re like see his work and
loving it and so yeah come tomorrow you
can definitely get to uh learn who J
Jason is um yeah yeah so yeah you guys
he's a very talented we had him on
hustle OWN Network um under the Monaco
Black Diamond show but we'll be bringing
him back back um and we got a lot of
people that are booked for the show and
hopefully uh Adrian will come back uh
for hustles on jam session hustles on
jam session is where uh where artists
mix in with the crowd and we have a
discussion we have an open discussion
about different things like politics and
stuff like that Adrian can we can we get
you to uh I didn't mean to drop you in
here quickly but like now you good yeah
got to stay hydrated horrible got to
stay hydrated
he's horrible I know uh could could we
get you to come into one of our hustles
own jam session shows it's live we got
like 10 people in the room and we just
ask uh questions about politics and and
whatnot and it's just an experience
where we bring the fans into the room
hell yeah see folks that's why you guys
got to follow us C he said hell
yeah okay talk to you later agent yeah
blessed yeah so
oh hold on a second so yeah we're gonna
we we have to um you're gonna have to
follow us because hustle Zone giant
session is one of the greatest shows
that we have uh we also have the talking
drum which we are working on um which
will be bringing on people to talk about
more racism and um a lot of social
issues and then of course go live and
prosper um where we talk to
entrepreneurs and and what have you so
hustle Zone as you guys know we're going
to have so much going on and then we
have the uh Nomad show that is going to
be coming back with um LS class and
Sandra Crespo uh with the first class RV
so like we are busy busy busy busy busy
so if you're not following us and if
you're watching this via YouTube right
now make sure to hit the the sub like
and the Subscribe button subscribe
button will show up and then hit the
notification Bell so that you are
notified that when we go live so folks
thank you guys all for joining and we
will talk to you guys later
bye okay hold on one second here
sorry
bye e